Hello friends.  Today's date is
31 sorry 21
April 2025 and the time is
6:58 i.e. 2 minutes are left for 7 o'clock.  At night
and today is Monday.  Ok?  Here we will
look at ICICI LBRD.  Who will you
look at?  We will do chart analysis of ICICI LBRD.
Before doing the analysis, a
disclaimer is given in the description box.  It
is important to read it.  Only after that you
will watch my video and watch the entire video.   If you
skip it, you will lose your knowledge.
Ok?  Here I
tell you with knowledge where to enter and exit.
Ok?  So if you want to gain knowledge then do
not skip and watch the video friends.
Watch the full video and
like the video as much as possible.  Ok?  And
subscribe to the channel because
you will not see this channel again.  If you do
not subscribe, you will
keep searching for the channel but will not find it.  Ok
?  Now let's see what he did?  So LBRD had
given a breakout here at
1595 i.e. had given a breakout near 1595.
After that I had a calculation target
and that target was 2110.   The
target was 2110 and see friends,
after giving breakout, it retraced once and then
took it straight
to 2100. Okay, understand friends, this
is a complete game of calculation, if you do
not understand this game, you will not be able to stay in the game,
how much did it go, friends, it went till 2300.  How far did it go
?  Went up to 2300.  Whereas
my target was 2112.  What happened after that
friends?  Could not sustain after touching 2300.
Friends, it could
not sustain this level and it started falling from there.
Where have you come again?   It fell around
1500, sorry 1600, around 1614.
Ok?
So that is why whenever we have a target,
it should be sustained on that target.  If it
cannot be sustained then there will be a huge
decline.  Ok?  That's why we say
exit on target.  Look
friends, always remember that entry and exit are
very important.  If you do
not enter and exit at the same time,
you will always have less profit
and more loss.  Ok?  forever
remember.  So this is a very big chapter.
Ok?  Chart analysis is
not a simple matter, friends.  This has to be analyzed.
You should know calculations.  If
you don't have the calculations, there's
no analysis to be done, right?  If it does not come, then
you will never be able to make profit from the market in your life.
Ok?  Because the entry will
not be at the right time and if the entry is
not at the right time then you will not be able to exit at the right time.
Ok?  Right now the
Lambor job here was entry level.
Which was the entry level?   The
1793 was the entry level.  Ok?
I will write it here.  Look, this is the
entry
level.  Entry
level.  Ok?  Where was the entry level?
In 1793.  Ok?  And it is currently running at 1845.  Ok.
So now its first target will be
1942.  How much will it cost?
1942.  What do you do now?  You have to
keep the stop loss small.  It should not be kept too big.
Okay, right?  Always play with stop loss
friends.  Ok?
So if I see the stop loss, at what level should I
place the stop loss, so you should place the stop loss,
if you enter at 1845 then
your stop loss should be at 1812, sorry,
you can place the stop loss at 1810, okay, at
what level should you place the stop loss at 1810,
that is, from here you can take a loss of approximately 30%, ah
sorry, 30 points.  Ok?   Do
n't take a big loss.  Ok?
You have to keep a stop loss of 1810.   Let's go to the
chart.
So the entry level is of 1793 and today it is
1845.  Ok?  So the entry has been made.  You
can take it if you want.  But
where should you place your stop loss now?  You will have to keep a stop loss of 1810.
Ok?  And the first target will be 1942 and the second
target will be
2150.  How much?  2150 means you can take a profit of 20% from here.
If you
take entry then you can earn 20% profit here.
Ok
?  What can you do?  You can earn.
After that I will make a video again.  When
it crosses.  Whom will he cross?
I will make a video again when it crosses 2150.  For now,
I will explain it further.  Then it will become very big.  Ok
?  So what will we do now?
For short term, let us take the target of 2150.
Where to place stop loss?  Place
stop loss at 1810.  Because 1845 is gone.
If you enter at 1845 then
your stop loss should be at 1810.  Ok
?  What is the target?  2150.  I am saying it again and again.  Take
note of it.  And here I
also enter the tax.  Ok?  2150 is my
target.
2150 means you can take a profit of 20% from here.
Ok?  So if you liked the video
then definitely press the like button.  It
is very simple to analyze the chart.  If you do
not know how to do analysis, do
not know calculations, I provide courses from basic to advanced
here.  If you don't want to do it with me
, then go to someone else.  Ok
?  Who can teach you this today?  Ok?  No
one will teach this.  Ok?  I will
give you complete practical knowledge here.  I
guarantee that I will take you to practical knowledge
and it is complete practical knowledge.  There
is no hassle of videos or PDFs here.  Direct
practical takes place here.  Ok?  The
analysis of the entire chart will be done on a
completely practical basis.  Ok
?  So if you liked the video then
definitely press the like button.  And if you want to learn then
brother, I will write my contact number here
and my contact number is also in the description,
you can contact me on 98273724.
Friends, if you feel that
if a comment comes from your side that
brother, please analyze this stock also, then
I will easily do it for you.  There
is no tension.  Please do write in the comment that Sir, please
analyze this stock and tell me.  So
I will quickly prepare it and upload it to you
in the video.  Ok?  So
join the Twitter channel.  Given in the description box.
Ok?  And subscribe to YouTube
and
share as many videos as possible friends.  Don't limit yourself.
Share the video with as many people as possible
so that the channel will grow and
those who want to earn money in this share market can
also earn profit.
Ok?  Chalo thank you for watching my
videos.